ehol.net 2013-04-23

# Privacy Policy | Ehol Nation

**Privacy Policy for Ehol**  
The following privacy statement covers everything about Ehol.net. Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Ehol users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Ehol does not endorse these comments as they are opinions of users not associated with Ehol.

**Mailing List**  
Ehol may launch a mailing list for Ehol. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address . This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However,Ehole has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Ehol. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on Ehol are delivered to users by third party advertisers including Google, among others. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) This site allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you and other  
Internet users visit. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,  
browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. Users may opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link [HERE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  
Ehol participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising within advertising units that link to<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Ehol may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Ehol.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Ehol changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.
